To localize and classify multiple objects in an image,
要定位并分类图像中的多个对象
we want to be able to identify a limited set of cropped regions for a CNN to look at.
我们希望能够识别有限数量的裁剪区域供 CNN 查看
In the ideal case,
在理想情况下
we would generate three perfectly cropped regions
我们将为图像中的三个不同对象
for three different objects in an image.
生成三个完美裁剪的区域
To approach this goal and generate a good limited set of cropped regions,
为了实现这一目标并生成数量合理的裁剪区域
the idea of region proposals was introduced.
诞生了候选区域的概念
Region proposals give us a way to quickly look at an image and generate
候选区域使我们能够快速查看图像
regions only for areas in which we think there may be an object.
并仅为我们认为可能存在对象的部分生成区域
We can use traditional computer vision techniques that detect things like edges and
我们可以使用传统计算机视觉技巧检测边缘和纹理 Blob 等
textured bobs to produce a set of regions in which objects are most likely to be found;
生成一组最后可能在其中发现对象的区域
areas of similar texture or the same unifying boundary, for example.
例如具有相似纹理的区域或相同的统一边界的区域
These proposals often produce noisy non-object regions,
这些建议通常会生成有噪非对象区域
but they are also very likely to include the regions in which objects are located.
但是也非常有可能包含具有对象的区域
So the noise is considered a worthwhile cost for not missing any objects.
因此噪点是值得考虑的 以防止忽略任何对象
So let's see how this looks when incorporated into a CNN architecture.
我们来看看此方法在 CNN 架构中的样貌如何
We can use a region proposal algorithm to produce a limited set of cropped regions.
我们可以使用候选区域算法生成一组有限的裁剪区域
Often called regions of interests or ROIs.
通常称之为感兴趣区域 (ROI)
And then we put these regions through a classification CNN,
然后将这些区域挨个地传入分类 CNN 中
one at a time and see what kind of class label the network predicts for each crop.
看看网络对每个裁剪区域预测出什么样的分类标签
This model is called an R-CNN.
这种模型称为 R-CNN
Which stands for region convolutional neural network.
是区域卷积神经网络的简称
The R-CNN produces a class for each region of interest,
R-CNN 为每个感兴趣区域生成一个类别
and so it can identify the region that is a dog and the region that is a cat in an image.
因此可以识别图像中有狗的区域和有猫的区域
In this case we also include a class called background,
在此示例中 我们还包含了一个类别 叫做背景
that's meant to capture any noisy regions.
用于捕获任何有噪区域
Since these regions are often different sizes they first need to be transformed and
因为这些区域通常具有不同的大小 因此首先需要被转换成标准大小
warped into a standard size that a CNN can accept as input.
使 CNN 能够接受为输入图像
Now, the main shortcoming of this method is that it still time intensive because it
这个方法的主要缺点是依然很耗时
requires that each cropped region go through
因为需要将每个裁剪区域传入整个 CNN 中
an entire CNN before a class label can be produced.
然后才能生成一个类别标签
Next, we'll see some examples of region-based CNNs that aim to speed up
接下来 我们将了解一些区域 CNN 示例
this process and efficiently classify multiple objects in an image.
这些 CNN 的目标是加速这一流程并有效分类图像中的多个对象